(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Midnight Aurora: A Winter Idol Night
The night shines brighter when she sings...
KOBO KANAERU
Special guests are here to join the fun so don't blink
KUREIJI OLLIE / AYUNDA RISU / AIRANI IOFIFTEEN / PAVOLIA REINE
VESTIA ZETA
SHIRAKAMI FUBUKI / SAKURA MIKO / MOCOCO ABYSSGARD / FUWAWA ABYSSGARD
OURO KRONII
NATSUYIRO MATSURI / OOZORA SUBARU
OTONOSE KANADE / TODOROKI HAJIME
NERISSA RAVENCROFT
HOUSHOU MARINE
The moment we've all been waiting for...
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです。 feat. 百沙子
I can't say that I love you feat. Hisako
ハオ...
Hao...
こんなことになるなんて
I never thought it would turn out like this
会う前には分かってたら
If only I'd known before we met
もう少しだけちゃんとした僕を
I could have shown you a version of myself
見せられたはずなんだ
that was a bit more put-together.
どうしたらいいのかなんて
What I should do
頭では分かってるけど
I know in my head, but...
何気ないちょっとした言葉で
Just a few casual words from you...
嬉し顔が出ちゃって
...and a happy look slips onto my face.
こんなバレバレじゃ格好悪いな
It's so obvious, it's embarrassing.
けどこのままじゃ引き下がれないよな
But I can't just back down like this.
でも今も顔照れくさくて
But even now, I'm feeling so shy...
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
I just can't bring myself to say I love you.
この気持ち伝わるかな
Will these feelings reach you?
言いたい、言いたい、キャラじゃない
I want to say it, but it's not like me.
何も言えずまたサヨナラ
I say goodbye again without saying a word.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much I can't stand it.
明日こそは言えるかな
I wonder if I'll be able to say it tomorrow.
あなたも僕と同じように恋してたら
If you were falling in love just like me,
なんて考えちゃうんだ
that's what I find myself thinking.
会えない日が続いてる
The days we can't meet keep going on.
このままじゃよろしくない
It's not looking good at this rate.
会ったところで何ができるって
Even if we met, what could I do?
わけじゃないんだけど
It's not that I have a plan, but...
こんな恋は二度とないな
A love like this will never happen again.
頭では分かってるけど
I know in my head, but...
眩しすぎその笑顔が
Your smile is just too dazzling...
僕を焦らせるんだ
...and it makes me panic.
ずっと見ていたくなるような
Like I want to keep looking at you forever,
目を逸らしたくなってしまうような
like I want to turn my eyes away...
こんな気持ち分かるのかな
I wonder if you understand this feeling.
あなたが笑ってるならそれでいいんです
If you're smiling, then that's enough.
でも隣は僕がいいな
But I wish it were me by your side.
もしかしたら実はずっと気づいてるんじゃないかな
Could it be that you've actually known all along?
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much I can't stand it.
言えるかな？
I wonder if I can say it?
全てをひっくり返すくらいの
Something that would flip everything upside down,
意気なセリフは
a witty line,
消えそうにないな
doesn't seem like it will come to mind.
どうしたってこの気持ちは
No matter what, this feeling
抑えられそうにはないんだ
cannot be suppressed.
あなたと出会ったあの日から
Since the day I met you,
ずっと気持ちは変わらない
my feelings haven't changed at all,
けど
but...
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです。
I just can't say that I love you.
この気持ち伝わるかな？
I wonder if these feelings will reach you?
空回り
Spinning my wheels,
何も言えずまた「さよなら」
I say "goodbye" again without saying a word.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much I can't stand it.
明日こそは言いたいな
I want to tell you tomorrow for sure.
あなたも僕と同じように
I wonder if you,
恋してたらなんて考えてる
feel the same way as I do.
でもわかってる
But I know,
考えすぎってこと
that I'm just overthinking it.
Kobo-Kobo-Kobo, Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me your sun to shine your day.
Hi everyone! Kobo-wa!
Kobo Kanaeru desu!
I'm Kobo Kanaeru!
Kobo no 3D seitan haishin e youkoso!
Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru's 3D Birthday Stream 2025!
Pachi-pachi-pachi!
How was Kobo's performance? Hmm? Hmm?
どうだった？
How was it?
またギターで出てきたよね？
I came out with my guitar again, didn't I?
ちょっと待って...
Wait a second...
Let me put the guitar down first.
おいしょ、おいしょ、おいしょ...
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho...
Okay! Once again,
Welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream 2025!
Koboの3D生誕配信へようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
This time, I, Kobo, will be hosting an...
idol-みたいなコンサート-themed
idol-like concert-themed
3D birthday stream for about an hour
with a lot of amazing and awesome guests.
I bet you guys can't wait!
Eh? Kobo,
voice-主が different?
my voice is different?
Ah, chat, nice eyes, chat! You noticed it!
Yeah, you're right! Look at Kobo's new stage!
わ！デカい！
Wow! It's huge!
新しいステージや！
It's a new stage!
There's a big Cilus right here...
大きなチルス...
A big Cilus...
ウニョウニョ...
Wriggle wriggle...
And so many stars!
Stars! So many stars!
And then a big, very big rainbow right here!
Big, very big rainbow!
And so many clouds because...
I don't know, I think it's just very aesthetic.
Yeah, and the floor!
フロア見て！
Look at the floor!
わ！なんかパターン...海みたい。
Wow! The pattern... looks like the ocean.
You know? Yeah, like my hair.
So, don't forget to take a lot of screenshots, okay?
Especially later, okay?
Get a lot of screenshots!
And then post your comments, your moments,
your impressions, everything with the hashtag
#3DKobornDay2025 on your SNS.
そして、Koboの3Dバースデー配信、
And please post your comments, memories,
SNSにハッシュタグ
impressions, and so on on SNS
#3DKobornDay2025 を付けて、
with the hashtag #3DKobornDay2025
コメントや思い出、
for Kobo's 3D
感想などなど投稿してね！
birthday stream!
Right! Are you guys ready for the next performance?
Okay, let's go to the next performance!
Wait, I try to remember...
My last expo... next expo...
あ、おっけー！歌います！
Ah, okay! I'm gonna sing!
それでは皆さん、準備いーかー？
Now then everyone, are you ready?
Let's go to the next song!
とくべチュして
Give Me a Special Kiss
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough
一番だいじがいい
I want to be your most important one
君が作るオリジナルの
Give me your original...
とくべチュして
...special kiss
眩しくて目が覚めて
It's so bright that I wake up
Oh yeah!
愛おしく思ってるよ
I'm thinking of you with love
Oh yeah!
眠り姫のように
Just like a Sleeping Beauty
優しく口づけて
Please kiss me gently
夢見てたこの世界
This world I've been dreaming of
Oh yeah!
誘惑かかる君がいる
There you are, so tempting
Oh yeah!
全てに触れずに
Without touching everything
二人だけでいよう
Let's stay just the two of us
私のこと独占して
Keep me all to yourself
君だけのものになってもいい
I don't mind belonging only to you
何でもある日の
On any given day
何でもない気づいてせめて
At least notice the little things
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough
君の特別にして
Make me your special one
でももっと give me a kiss more
But give me even more of a kiss
私は君でいっぱいよ
I'm completely full of you
解けないリボン結び
An untieable ribbon knot
小指きゅっと縛って
Tie our pinkies tightly together
そうよ一生一生がいいの
Yes, forever and ever is what I want
特別中が欲しい
I want a special attention
二人きり週末は
On the weekends when we're alone
Oh yeah!
奏でてよハーモニー
Please play a harmony
Oh yeah!
流星群見たら
If we see a meteor shower
私を想ってほしい
I want you to think of me
甘々君なのに
Even though you're so sweet
Oh yeah!
広い街吸い込まれ
Getting sucked into the wide city
Oh yeah!
戦う姿に
To your fighting figure
大きな花丸だね
I'll give you a big gold star
好きなとこ優しいとこ
What I like, your kindness
嫌いなとこも優しいとこ
Even what I dislike, your kindness
誰にもあげない
I won't give you to anyone
私だけ独り占め
I'll keep you all to myself
だって今までの人と
Because, compared to everyone before
同じはいらないんです
I don't want the same things
でももっと give me your love
But give me even more of your love
私のために生きてほしいんです
I want you to live for my sake
だからうさぎと私は
That's why a rabbit and I
寂しくさせないで
Don't let us be lonely
それじゃ束縛じゃないわ
That's not being possessive
狂おしいのが好き
I like it when it's driving me crazy
ショートケーキ苺みたいに
Like a strawberry on a shortcake
座っててもいい？
Can I sit right there?
赤く甘い恋だもん
It's a red, sweet love after all
誰が磨き上げた？
Who was it that polished it?
大好きも返してもらって
Give me back all my love
全部私に頂戴
Give it all to me
もっと！
More!
君は神様が作る
You are like a miracle
奇跡のような人
Created by God himself
拗ねた顔もその寝顔も
Your pouting face and sleeping face
守ってあげるね Yeah!
I will protect them for you, yeah!
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough
君の特別にして
Make me your special one
でももっと give me a kiss more
But give me even more of a kiss
私は君でいっぱいよ
I'm completely full of you
解けないリボン結び
An untieable ribbon knot
小指きゅっと縛って
Tie our pinkies tightly together
ねえベイビー最初で最後の
Hey baby, make me your first and last...
特別にしてね
...special one
うわあああああああ！
Waaaaaaah!
天天天国地獄 (feat. ななひら & P丸様。)
Tenten Heaven Hell (feat. Nanahira & P-maru-sama)
テン！テン！テン！テン！テン！テン！テン！
Ten! Ten! Ten! Ten! Ten! Ten! Ten!
テンテン天国地獄地獄
Tenten heaven hell hell
Open Sesame!
闇と光の交わるアルファベット
The alphabet where light and dark intersect
今宵味わうサイケデリック
Savoring the psychedelic tonight
踊り絡まりあうゾディアック
The zodiac dancing and intertwining
恋の駆け引きのタイブレーク
The tie-break of love's strategies
抗えない存在
An irresistible existence
ただ気を惹きたい
Just want to get your attention
夢見心地触れ合い
Dreamlike physical contact
惑わせたい
Want to enchant you
曖昧解けないココ掘れワンワン
Vague and unsolvable, dig here woof-woof
…色合いは甘い
...the color is sweet
鮮やかな赤い愛
A vivid red love
見つめて限界
Staring until the limit
月夜に誘われ
Invited by the moonlit night
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a demon
天使と悪魔が甘さ消した
The angel and demon erased the sweetness
天国地獄の
Heaven and hell's
狭間で出会った
We met in the gap between
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a demon
天使と悪魔が集って踊れば
When the angel and demon gather and dance
天国地獄の
Heaven and hell's
天国地獄の門が開く
The gates of heaven and hell open
闇と光の交わるファナティック
A fanatic intersection of light and dark
今宵味わうサイケデリック
Tonight we taste the psychedelic
踊り絡み合うゾディアック
Dancing and intertwining Zodiac
恋の駆け引きのダイブブレイク
A dive break of love's tactics
DEAD OR ALIVE
Death Death Death Birth Birth Birth
Birth Birth Let's go!
生きた魂をトレイに置いて
Place your living soul on the tray
巡る五枚のカード 揺れる炎
The five cards revolve, a swaying flame
先にあなたがレイズしたならば
If you are the first to raise
もう迷わないグラス飲み干して
I won't hesitate anymore, drain the glass
今夜オールイン下りないこの勝負
Tonight I'm all in, I won't back down from this match
今、天国と地獄を繋ぐ門が開いていく。
Now, the gate connecting heaven and hell is opening.
天使と悪魔、死者と聖者が入り乱れ、
Angel and demon, the dead and the saint mingle,
踊り、笑い、
Dancing, laughing,
すべては混沌の中に飲み込まれていく。
everything is swallowed into the chaos.
それは世界の終焉であり、新たなる始まりでもあったのだ！
It was the end of the world, and also a new beginning!
DEAD OR ALIVE
Death Death Death Birth Birth Birth
Death Death Death Birth Birth Birth Birth
天！天！天！天！天国！
Heav! Heav! Heav! Heav! Heaven!
天！天！天！天！天国地獄！
Heav! Heav! Heav! Heav! Heaven and hell!
天！天！天！天！天国！
Heav! Heav! Heav! Heav! Heaven!
天！天！天！天！天国地獄！
Heav! Heav! Heav! Heav! Heaven and hell!
月夜に誘われ
Invited by the moonlit night
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a demon
天使と悪魔が甘さ消した
The angel and demon erased the sweetness
天国地獄の
Heaven and hell's
恍惚消えない果てないMoonlight
Ecstasy that won't fade, endless Moonlight
天国地獄の
Heaven and hell's
狭間で出会った
We met in the gap between
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a demon
天使と悪魔が集って踊れば
When the angel and demon gather and dance
天国地獄の
Heaven and hell's
狭間で出会った
We met in the gap between
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a demon
天使と悪魔が踊って踊れば
When the angel and demon dance and dance
Dance Dance Dance!
DEAD OR ALIVE
天国地獄！
Heaven and hell!
DEAD OR ALIVE
Death Death Death
天国地獄！
Heaven and hell!
DEAD OR ALIVE
天国地獄！
Heaven and hell!
DEAD OR ALIVE
Death Death Birth Birth!
天国地獄！GO!
Heaven and hell! GO!
やばい...
Oh my god...
イブリス dari mana kamu?
Where did this demon come from?
え？
Eh?
イブリス dari mana?
Where are you from, demon?
Wah, dikatain orang iblis, wah wah.
Wow, being called a demon by someone, wow wow.
Wahai!
Hey!
Itu empat tanduk bahaya sekali.
Those four horns are very dangerous.
Iya, jadi gini...
Yeah, so the thing is...
Aku datang jauh-jauh...
I've come from far away...
Ya, jauh-jauh...
Yeah, from far away...
Apa? Meskipun tidak diundang?
What? Even though you weren't invited?
Ah, diundang!
Ah, I was invited!
Iya, kayaknya kamu ngundang yang lain deh tadi.
Yeah, it seems like you invited someone else earlier.
Ma... ma... maksudnya?
Wh... wh... what do you mean?
どういう意味？
What do you mean?
Kenapa tiba-tiba 日本語？
Why suddenly Japanese?
Kamu malaikat Jepang ya?
Are you a Japanese angel?
Bisa berhenti muter? Pusing.
Can you stop spinning? I'm dizzy.
Pusing?
Dizzy?
Ya udah dah dah.
Okay then, bye-bye.
Aduh, malaikat kok pusing guys.
Man, how can an angel be dizzy, guys.
Iya, aku di sini soalnya datang buat ngerayu kamu aja sebenarnya.
Yeah, I'm here because I actually came to seduce you.
Pengen main bareng, pengen godain kamu aja.
I want to play together, I just want to tease you.
Sini sini sini...!
Come here, come here, come here...!
Pulang kamu habis ini. Loh, kamu habis ini pulang sama aku kan?
Go home after this. Eh, you're going home with me after this, right?
Pulang?
Go home?
Iya, habis ini nggak ada apa-apa lagi kan?
Yeah, there's nothing else after this, right?
Ngapain enak-enak aku di atas.
Why am I having such a good time up here.
Masa kamu seret aku?
Are you going to drag me?
Loh, loh, kita...
Eh, eh, we...
Kita, kita, lo aja iblis!
We, we, you're the one who's a demon!
Ajak dong!
Invite me then!
Ajak dong banget!
Invite me so much!
Kamu saya ajak.
I'll invite you.
Aku kesepian.
I'm lonely.
Ayo sini bareng.
Come here with me.
Fallen angel nih!
A fallen angel here!
Nggak nggak, nggak ada fallen angel, nggak ada nggak ada.
No no, there's no fallen angel, none at all.
Eits, nih aku panah.
Eits, I'll shoot you.
Iya iya.
Yeah yeah.
Coba coba.
Try it.
Panah asmara!
Arrow of love!
Satu, dua, tiga!
One, two, three!
Ya iya!
Yes yes!
Wah gila gila!
Wow, crazy crazy!
How to tame your demon.
Jadi light novel.
It's become a light novel.
Eh gimana tadi freestyle kita? Keren banget ya guys?
So, how was our freestyle earlier? Really cool, right guys?
Iya lucu gak?
Yeah, was it cute?
Atas.
Up.
Bawah.
Down.
Atas.
Up.
Bawah.
Down.
Atas.
Up.
Terus tadi pas kamu atas, aku bawah. Hahaha.
And then when you were up, I was down. Hahaha.
Kebalik.
Reversed.
Sengaja orang mah kebalik kiri kanan, dia kebalik atas bawah.
Normally people reverse left and right, but she reverses up and down.
Atas!
Up!
Atas.
Up.
Aku bawah.
I'm down.
Atas!
Up!
Kocak-kocak.
Wacky, wacky.
Ya udah.
Alright then.
Ya udah kalau gitu, aku... aku wanita sibuk ya sebenarnya.
Alright then, I'm... I'm actually a busy woman.
Jadi kayak emang gak ada... gak gitu banyak waktu.
So I don't really have... I don't have that much time.
Busyet.
My goodness.
Aku di sini mampir... mampir dikit aja bentaran.
I just stopped by here... just for a little bit.
Kasih tiga... kasih lima detik buat kamu.
Giving three... five seconds for you.
Busyet. Pemimpin Jigoku nih.
My goodness. The leader of Hell.
Asik!
Nice!
Oke.
Okay.
Baik.
Good.
Fiksi ya guys, ini cerita fiksi.
It's fiction guys, this is a fictional story.
Jangan ditiru adik-adik.
Don't copy this, kids.
Fiksi, fiksi ya guys.
Fiction, it's fiction guys.
Sensitif ini sensitif.
This is sensitive, sensitive.
Fiksi, bohongan.
Fiction, just kidding.
Oke kalau gitu, bye!
Okay then, bye!
Gak mau ikut aku lagi?
Don't want to come with me anymore?
Bye bye bye bye!
Jagain ini anak ya guys.
Take care of this kid, guys.
Kita lihat perilakunya beneran seiso atau enggak.
Let's see if her behavior is actually wholesome or not.
Lihat tuh lihat bajunya. Jagain jagain.
Look, look at her clothes. Watch her, watch her.
Ya udah, bye!
Alright then, bye!
Bisa jadi Fallen Angel aku karena hasutan dia, guys.
I might become a Fallen Angel because of her instigation, guys.
Gak jelas.
Absurd.
どきどきキュン！で大騒走♡
Heart-pounding Kyuun! Running Wild Around♡
なんとかしなくちゃならなくて
I had to do something
突然メイドになっちゃって
And suddenly I became a maid
いつものようにお店のお掃除
Cleaning the shop as usual
扉開いちゃって目が合った
The door opened and our eyes met
なんだかそわそわしちゃって
Somehow I got restless
あわてんぼうにもなっちゃって
And I got clumsy too
お仕事中に推しに夢中に
Obsessed with my oshi during work
どこをさがしても見当たらないじゃん
I can't find them anywhere
もう一回
One more time
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
もーいいよ
Enough already
秘密だよね
It's a secret, right?
もーいいの
It's fine now
好きになっちゃって
I've fallen in love
ねぇ「好き」って言って
Hey, say "I love you"
どきどきキュン！贈るラブビーム
Heart-pounding Kyuun! Sending a love beam
君も夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that makes you obsessed too
ほらどきどきキュン！私大暴走
Look, heart-pounding Kyuun! I'm running wild
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
The taste of love that makes you obsessed
もー君にキュン！私大迷走
Already Kyuun for you! I'm totally lost
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that makes us obsessed together
だから君がキュンってなる恋に落ちて
So fall in a love that makes you Kyuun
ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
Here's one for you, this is the taste of love
楽しくて仕方なかったって
It was so much fun, I couldn't help it
そろそろ終わりになっちゃって
It's almost time for it to end
会いたくなって落ち込んじゃって
I want to see you, I'm feeling down
君とぶつかって目が合った
I bumped into you and our eyes met
何度も会いたくなっちゃって
I wanted to see you over and over again
今日だけじゃ足りないんだって
Today alone isn't enough
計画通り！私の勝利
Just as planned! My victory
君に会いたくて仕方が無いよ
I can't help but want to see you
もう一回
One more time
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
もーいいの
It's fine now
君だけだよ
It's only you
もーずっと
Always
愛し合いたいよ
I want us to love each other
ねぇ「好き」って言って
Hey, say "I love you"
どきどきキュン！君にラブビーム
Heart-pounding Kyuun! A love beam for you
二人夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that makes us both obsessed
ほらどきどきキュン！私大恋愛
Look, heart-pounding Kyuun! My great romance
君も夢中にさせる恋のマキ
The story of love that makes you obsessed too
もー君にキュン！私大混乱
Already Kyuun for you! I'm in total chaos
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that makes us obsessed together
だから君がキュンってなる恋に落ちて
So fall in a love that makes you Kyuun
ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
Here's one for you, this is the taste of love
はわー このままだったら
Hawa... If it stays like this
ここで会うこともなくなって
We might never meet here again
うわー 君の声が
Uwaa... Your voice
聞きたくなるの
I want to hear it
もう一回
One more time
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
もーいいの
It's fine now
秘密なのに
Even though it's a secret
もーいいよ
Enough already
このまま好きになっていく
Falling in love just like this
「好き」って言って
Say "I love you"
どきどきキュン！贈るラブビーム
Heart-pounding Kyuun! Sending a love beam
君も夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that makes you obsessed too
ほらどきどきキュン！私大暴走
Look, heart-pounding Kyuun! I'm running wild
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
The taste of love that makes you obsessed
もー君にキュン！私大迷走
Already Kyuun for you! I'm totally lost
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that makes us obsessed together
だから君がキュンってなる恋に落ちて
So fall in a love that makes you Kyuun
ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
Here's one for you, this is the taste of love
Halo semuanya!
Hello everyone!
Hehe, langit sudah mulai gelap.
Hehe, the sky is starting to get dark.
Tapi masih pada semangat nggak semuanya?
But are you all still excited?
Whoo!
さっきアズぺコさんとパフォーマンスしてから、
After performing with AzPeko just now,
次はコボはまた一人で歌いたいなと思います。
Kobo wants to sing alone again for the next part.
これから歌うこの曲は最近コボが気に入っている曲で、
The song I'm about to sing is one I've been liking lately,
聴いたら幸せな気持ちになりました。
and listening to it made me feel happy.
皆さんもこの曲を聴いて幸せを感じてくれたら嬉しいです。
I'd be glad if you all feel happy listening to this song too.
それでは、次の曲、青山テルマさんの...
And now, the next song, by Thelma Aoyama...
Happiness です。
is Happiness.
思えるよ
...I can believe it
何も言わなくても
Even without saying anything
感じてるよ No one for me
I can feel it, you're the one for me
Happiness
Lyrics: 青山テルマ、H.U.B. / Music: 坂詰美紗子
Lyrics: Thelma Aoyama, H.U.B. / Music: Misako Sakazume
Oh oh oh
You always make me happy
落ち込んで眠れなくて
Feeling down and unable to sleep
君との写真 見つめている
I'm gazing at the photos of us
いくつもの笑顔たちに
By all those smiling faces
助けられるよ My life
I am saved, in my life
ずっと一緒だよ 泣いてもいいよ
We're always together, it's okay to cry
あの涙を 抱きしめてくれた
You embraced those tears
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ここにいるから
I'm right here
すぐに会いたいって
Saying "I want to see you soon"
きっと Happiness
Surely this is happiness
君がいれば 大丈夫だって思えるよ
If you're here, I feel like everything will be okay
何も言わなくても
Even without saying anything
感じてるよ No one for me
I can feel it, you're the one for me
君と Happiness
Happiness with you
どんな時も 一人じゃないって信じてるよ
I believe that no matter when, I'm not alone
涙あふれたって
Even if tears overflow
歩けるね Please stay by my side
I can keep walking, please stay by my side
君に出会えてからは
Since the moment I met you
素直に笑っていられるよ
I can smile honestly
少しずつ自分のこと
Bit by bit, myself
好きになった For your love
I've come to like, for your love
そう今なら
Yes, if it's now
ねえ心から わかり合えるって思えるよ
Hey, from my heart, I feel we can understand each other
強がらずに
Without acting tough
ありのままで 見つめてくれた
You gazed at me just as I am
だから Happiness
That's why, happiness
君のことも 今よりももっと知りたくて
I want to know more about you than I do now
どんな言葉よりも
More than any words
大切なよ No one for me
You're precious, the one for me
私も君に何か
I also want to do something
できることしたいよ
something for you
いつでも一緒だから
Because we're always together
守っていけるから
Because I can protect you
ずっと...
Forever...
きっと Happiness
Surely this is happiness
君がいれば 大丈夫だって思えるよ
If you're here, I feel like everything will be okay
何も言わなくても
Even without saying anything
感じてるよ No one for me
I can feel it, you're the one for me
君と Happiness
Happiness with you
どんな時も 一人じゃないって信じてるよ
I believe that no matter when, I'm not alone
涙あふれたって
Even if tears overflow
歩けるね Please stay by my side
I can keep walking, please stay by my side
大切なよ No one for me
You're precious, the one for me
Let's go!
Oh oh oh
You always make me happy
Smile for me baby
Oh oh oh
You always make me happy
Smile for me baby
Oh oh oh
You always make me happy
モエチャッカファイア
Lyrics, Music: 弌誠
Moe Chaka Fire
Lyrics, Music: Issei
よくぞお越しなすったご主人様
Welcome, Master.
お隣どうぞ せーの
Please sit next to me. Ready, go!
萌え 萌え 萌え 萌え
Moe moe moe moe
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who's going to be happy with this?
寝を強いて 笑顔でアップップ
Forcing sleep, puffing out with a smile.
理想は逸れてご苦労様
Thanks for your hard work, even if it's off the ideal path.
私とあなたで せーの
Between me and you. Ready, go!
LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who's going to be happy with this?
寝を強いて 笑顔でアップップ
Forcing sleep, puffing out with a smile.
ヒラリハラリ女の子
A girl fluttering around.
ふわりふわり言葉のソレ
Fluffy words, that kind of thing.
それでつまり収めなきゃ
So, in short, I have to keep it in check.
感情的リアル 笑顔でアップップ
Emotional reality, puffing out with a smile.
人は見かけによらぬもの
Don't judge a person by their appearance.
嘘を嘘と見抜けない
Can't tell if a lie is a lie.
したたかな袖 裾ん皮
A tough sleeve, a leather hem.
あー 鳥肌 寒気 アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Ah, goosebumps, chills, un, deux, trois.
待ち焦がれた末召し上がれ
After longing for it, please enjoy.
いただきます
Bon appétit.
私とあなたで せーの
Between me and you. Ready, go!
LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE
これはド派手にご苦労様
Thanks for your flashy work.
遊びましょう 笑顔でアップップ
Let's play, puffing out with a smile.
ヒラリハラリここはどこ
Fluttering around, where am I?
ふわりふわり外は内緒
Fluffy, fluffy, what's outside is a secret.
それでつまり収めなきゃ
So, in short, I have to keep it in check.
感情的リアル 笑顔でアップップ
Emotional reality, puffing out with a smile.
歌い出す 秘密の金
Starting to sing, secret money.
終わることのないこの世界
This world that never ends.
悲しい子供は 虚しい子供は
Sad children, empty children.
眠らせて
Lull them to sleep.
おままごと 遊びましょう
Playing house, let's play.
笑顔でアップップ
Puffing out with a smile.
ヒラリハラリ女の子
A girl fluttering around.
ふわりふわり言葉のソレ
Fluffy words, that kind of thing.
それでつまり収めなきゃ
So, in short, I have to keep it in check.
感情的リアル 笑顔でアップップ
Emotional reality, puffing out with a smile.
遊びましょう 笑顔でアップップ
Let's play, puffing out with a smile.
アップップ
Puffing out.
Let's dance with me!
SUNDAY NIGHT MAGIC
Lyrics: TINA, KMNCrew Music: Hisaki TOMIYAMA, RIKE
何回でも起きるTRUE MAGIC
TRUE MAGIC that happens over and over.
まだまだ今日は夢見心地
I'm still feeling like I'm dreaming today.
夜目が覚めても COME BACK AGAIN
Even if I wake up at night, COME BACK AGAIN.
何度でも奏でよう 朝が来るその時まで
Let's play over and over, until the morning comes.
ねぇ 僕とどうだい
Hey, how about with me?
塞ぎ込んでる週の終わりに
At the end of a week feeling down,
退屈そうだけど どうだろう
you look bored, but how about it?
誘っていいかな
Can I invite you?
COME NIGHT COME NIGHT COME WAKKANAI
こっち向いてる こっち向いてる
Looking this way, looking this way.
あっち向いてホイなんかじゃなくて
It's not about playing 'look that way, hoy'.
君のことだもん もっとちゃんと話聞いてよ
Since it's about you, listen to me properly.
HEY 列席から逆転
HEY, a reversal from the seats.
金曜より今日の方が可愛いし
Today is even cuter than Friday.
居ても立っても居られない
I can't just sit still.
聞こえるぜ 0時告げるチャイム
I can hear it, the chime announcing midnight.
時間切れのその先へ
Beyond the time limit.
飛び出して 駆け出して
Jump out, run out.
まだまだ夜は終われない
The night can't end yet.
こんな最高の毎日が
If such perfect days
明日も続いてくんなら
were to continue tomorrow too,
ねぇ 君もどうだい
hey, how about you too?
待ち望んでる君の理想の
The princess's seat you've been
お姫様の席をどうしよう
waiting for, what should I do with it?
狙っていいかな
Can I aim for it?
MAKE CHANCE LAST CHANCE 今じゃない？
MAKE CHANCE LAST CHANCE, isn't it now?
猫も杓子も曲に合わせて
Everyone and everything, to the music,
ステップなんか踏んでみて
try taking some steps.
ご機嫌いかが
How are you feeling?
金曜より今日が ずっと楽しくて
Today is much more fun than Friday.
続けたい時には
When I want to keep going,
聞こえるぜ 0時告げるチャイム
I can hear it, the chime announcing midnight.
時間切れのその先へ
Beyond the time limit.
終わらない 止まらない
It won't end, it won't stop.
まだまだ夜は長いから
Because the night is still long.
こんな最高の毎日
Such perfect days...
心に 身体を預けてみたら
If you try surrendering your heart and body...
ほら 魔法みたいだ
Look, it's like magic.
Leave it to the club, cuz this world
騒がしくて 馬鹿らしいような
A noisy and seemingly foolish...
エンタープライズな毎日がいい
...enterprise-like every day is fine.
魔法なんて あり得ない
Magic is impossible.
でも 今夜だけは現実になるかも
But tonight, it might just become a reality.
アナログなステップで 音に登って
Climbing the sound with analog steps,
驚け 君も
You should be surprised too!
終わらない夜に とびきりの魔法
An extraordinary magic for an endless night.
君にも かけてあげるから
I'll cast it on you too,
僕の手をとってよ
So take my hand.
震える鳴り止まないミュージック
Trembling music that won't stop ringing.
魔法が解けるまで
Until the magic wears off...
最高で最強な夜が
The ultimate and strongest night...
今日も更けていく
...grows deeper again today.
こんな夢みたいな日々が
If these dream-like days...
明日も続いてくなら
...were to continue tomorrow too...
ねえ 君はどうだい？
Hey, how about you?
アンコール 大胆に夜を飾るソング
Encore! A song that boldly decorates the night.
何回でもかける 超マジ
I'll play it as many times as it takes, super serious.
まだまだ夢心地
Still feeling like I'm in a dream.
嘘みたいだけど
It seems like a lie, but...
朝が来るその時まで
...until the time the morning comes...
ねえ 僕と踊らい
Hey, dance with me.
うわあ！キャー！ここどこ？
Whoa! Kyaa! Where are we?
わかんない！
I don't know!
え、なんか雲美味しそうじゃね？
Eh, don't the clouds look delicious?
食べてみようよ。
Let's try eating them.
(食べる音)
(Eating sounds)
お、美味しい！
Oh, it's delicious!
美味しい！
It's delicious!
イェーイ！
Yay!
じゃあ次ちょっと何食べ...
Then next, let's eat...
何をしてるの！
What are you doing?!
こぼちゃーん！おいしかったおいしかった
Kobo-chan! It was delicious, delicious!
あ、始めは食べてないです！
Ah, we didn't eat them at first!
うう、見守ってた見守ってた！
Uu, we were watching over them, watching over them!
私の雲をー！
My clouds!
ああ、誰が...
Ah, who...
こぼちゃーん！始めは食べてないです！
Kobo-chan! We didn't eat them at first!
チャチャモニャ！チャチャモニャ！
Chachamonya! Chachamonya!
「うー」じゃないんだよ！
Don't give me that "uu"!
何をしてるの！
What are you doing?!
落ち着いて！今日は誕生日だよ！
Calm down! Today is your birthday!
やっちょー！
Yay!
誕生日！ハッピーバースデー！
Birthday! Happy Birthday!
あ、ありがとう！
A-Ah... thank you!
イェーイ！ようこそようこそ！
Yay! Welcome, welcome!
え、じゃあ、こぼ先輩と一緒に歌って踊りたい！
Eh, then, I want to sing and dance with Kobo-senpai!
歌って踊りたい！
I want to sing and dance!
アン・ドゥ・トロワ！
Un, deux, trois!
OK OK OK. こぼの振り付け！
OK OK OK. Kobo's choreography!
こぼの振り付け。ベリーナイス！
Kobo's choreography. Very nice!
こぼの、え、こぼ先生と呼んでください。
Kobo's... eh, please call me Kobo-sensei.
こぼこちゃーん！
Koboko-chan!
ガキだから言わせない！
You're a brat so I won't let you say it!
(叫び声)
(Screaming)
うん。
Yeah.
じゃ、勉強した？
So, did you study?
もちろん！勉強した！
Of course! I studied!
コレオグラフィーや。
It's choreography.
コレオグラフィーな。
Choreography, right.
じゃ、行きましょう！
Then, let's go!
イェーイ、行きましょう！
Yay, let's go!
おーいいじゃん！
Oh, nice!
欲ししゅのっけ！
Hoshishunokke!
OK!
OK OK, じゃ、行きましょう。
OK OK, then let's go.
月夜のアン・ドゥ・トロワ
Lyrics, Music: DATEKEN
Gekigetsu Un Deux Trois
誰もいなくなった
Nobody is around anymore.
二人だけの街に
In this town for just the two of us...
機械仕掛けの時計が
...a mechanical clock...
夜の訪れ知らせる
...announces the arrival of night.
夕闇が空を
The twilight dyes the sky...
ワイン色に染めて
...in the color of wine...
不慣れな二人を
...beckoning our awkward selves...
舞台へと誘う
...to the stage.
Just away, and up to top
あなたに魔法あげる
I'll cast a spell on you.
To away, and up to way
その名前はハニミ
Its name is Hanimy.
三つ数えアン・ドゥ・トロワ
Count to three, un deux trois.
互いの指を絡めて
Entwining our fingers together.
Singing swinging swing the song...
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing out our dream
月光アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Gekkou Un Deux Trois
Chase and whisk and natural tour...
あなたに魔法をかける
I'll cast a spell on you
Throw away and oversway...
魅惑の蜜に、ハニーミー
In the enchanting nectar, honey me
見つけて アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Find me, un, deux, trois
どの唇を 重ねて
Which lips should meet?
Singing swinging swing the song...
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing out our love
月明かりの路
The moonlit path
黄金色に照らして
Shines in gold
お揃い 二人は
Together, the two of us
つまずきながら 踊る
Dance while stumbling along
見つけて アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Find me, un, deux, trois
互いの指を 絡めて
Entwining our fingers
Singing swinging swing the song...
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing out our dream
見つけて アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Find me, un, deux, trois
その唇を 重ねて
Let our lips meet
Singing swinging swing the song...
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing out our love
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
やっほー！
Yay!
Woi!
Dancenya jago! Dancenya jago!
Your dancing is good! Your dancing is good!
Pastinya! Terima kasih!
Of course! Thank you!
Nanka um... suwan.
Something like... swannish.
コボ先輩もシュワン。
Kobo-senpai is also swannish.
シュワン！
Swannish!
奏先輩シュワン！
Kanade-senpai is swannish!
シュワン シュワン シュワン シュワン！
Swannish swannish swannish swannish!
Beautiful suwan!
Beautiful swannish!
Beneran elegant!
Truly elegant!
ありがとコボコボ！
Thank you, Kobo-kobo!
Hore Kobo-chan dancenya jago!
See, Kobo-chan's dancing is good!
難しかったー。
That was hard.
A little bit... 大丈夫、えいあー！
A little bit... it's okay, eiaaaa!
Easy easy!
Easy なの？
Was it easy?
Easy じゃないよ...
It wasn't easy...
楽しかった！
It was fun!
見てくれてありがとね！
Thanks for watching!
奏先輩、呼んでくれてありがちょ！
Kanade-senpai, thanks for coming!
ありがとコボコボ！
Thanks, Kobo-kobo!
一緒に踊ってくれてもありがと！
Thanks for dancing with me too!
Terima kasih!
Thank you!
Sama-sama!
You're welcome!
Nyama nyama nyama nyama...
Happy Birthday!
おめでと！
Congratulations!
Happy Birthday!
Hwaiting!
じゃあ、バイバイ！
Well then, bye bye!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
みんな帰っちゃった...
Everyone went home...
寂しい...
I'm lonely...
悲しい...
I'm sad...
誰も来ないのかな...
I wonder if no one else is coming...
でも、
Demo,
But...
さよならの前に キスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye
さよならの後は 忘れさせて
After goodbye, let me forget
でも あなたの名前が 消えない
But your name won't disappear
離れない 離さない
I won't leave, I won't let go
戻りたい
I want to go back
Take me free.
この恋は君がいた
You were in this love
あの日みたい
Just like that day
二人を彩るこの街並み
These city streets that color the two of us
部屋の中は香水代わりのソフィアのフレーバー
The room is filled with Sophia's flavor instead of perfume
当たり前さえも奇跡
Even the ordinary is a miracle
当たり障れない君との軌跡
The harmless path with you
どれだけ恋知っても 越えられない君を
No matter how much love I know, I can't surpass you
今ならわかる気がして
I feel like I understand now
今から過去にも戻れるなら
If I could go back to the past from now
サヨナラの前に キスをして
Before the goodbye, give me a kiss
サヨナラの後は 忘れさせて
After the goodbye, let me forget
でも あなたの名前が 消えない
But your name won't fade away
離れない 離さない 戻りたい
Won't leave, won't let go, want to go back
Take me free
呪いたいほど 愛しているのよ
I love you so much it's like a curse
気づけば あなたのことばかり浮かべて
Before I know it, I'm only thinking of you
明日になれば 大丈夫
If tomorrow comes it'll be fine
何度言い聞かせればいいの
How many times do I have to tell myself?
愛という沼に 溺れてる
I'm drowning in a swamp called love
私の声は 届くかな
Will my voice reach you?
サヨナラの前に キスをして
Before the goodbye, give me a kiss
サヨナラの後は 忘れさせて
After the goodbye, let me forget
でも あなたの名前が 消えない
But your name won't fade away
離れない 離さない 戻りたい
Won't leave, won't let go, want to go back
Take me free サヨナラの前に キスをして
Take me free, before the goodbye, give me a kiss
サヨナラの後は 忘れさせて
After the goodbye, let me forget
でも あなたの名前が 消えない
But your name won't fade away
離れない 離さない 戻りたい
Won't leave, won't let go, want to go back
Take me free
変えない日々 抱きしめたまま
While embracing the unchanging days
Closing
Lyrics: 下川美帆、満田尚子 Music: 下川美帆
Lyrics: Miho Shimokawa, Naoko Mitsuda Music: Miho Shimokawa
いつか そう いつか
Someday, yes, someday
弱い心が 捕まる前に
Before my weak heart gets caught
そっと あなたを遠ざけた
I gently pushed you away
ああ こんな気持ち
Ah, this feeling
辛すぎるよ もう
It's just too painful
あなたは 誰なの?
Who are you?
どこに 隠れてたの?
Where were you hiding?
ひどく 怯えてる
I'm terribly afraid
俯いたままの
Still looking down
見送るな 私が
Don't see me off, I...
願ってた
...was wishing
またあの季節 夜空は白く
That season again, the night sky is white
あなたも いて
You are there too
触れてこないで 嬉しいけど
Don't touch me, I'm happy but...
心が 痛い
...my heart hurts
離したくない 離れたくない
I don't want to let go, I don't want to leave
でも 諦めてた
But I had given up
もうこれ以上 好きになれない
I can't love you any more than this
失う痛み 耐えきれないよ
I can't bear the pain of losing you
変えない日々 抱きしめたまま
While embracing the unchanging days
いつか そう いつか
Someday, yes, someday
ただそばにいて それだけでいい
Just be by my side, that's all I need
素直にはなれないけれど
Though I can't be honest with you
さあ顔を上げて
Come on, lift your head
歩き始めなきゃ
I have to start walking
リアルな私を
Realize the...
気づいて
...real me
またあの季節
That season again
この空の下
Under this sky
見上げている
I'm looking up
傷ついたもの
Things that were hurt
もう元には
Can't ever go...
戻らないけれど
...back to how they were
離したくない
I don't want to let go
離れたくない
I don't want to be apart
もう諦めない
I won't give up anymore
あなたの心
Your heart...
傷つけてでも
...even if I hurt it
自分の気持ちに
My feelings...
嘘はつけない
...I can't lie to them
いつか笑顔で
One day with a smile
話せるような
Being able to talk
私を見つけて
Find me
傍にいて
Stay by my side
聞かせて欲しい
I want you to tell me
二度と一人には
That you'll never...
しないと
...leave me alone again
帰らない日々
Days that won't return
抱きしめたまま
While holding onto them
きっとそうきっと
Surely, yes, surely
あの日の気持ち
My feelings from that day
受け止めないと
I have to accept them
前に進む
Move forward
ことができない
I can't do it
離したくない
I don't want to let go
離れたくない
I don't want to be apart
一つの願いは
My one wish is...
大好きだよと
...that I love you
伝えたいだけ
I just want to tell you
本当素直じゃ
I'm really not...
ないけれど
...honest, but...
So...
How is it, guys?
That was "Closing".
Hmm?
Did you take a lot of screenshots? Ooh!
And ah, how about my new stage?
Look! Wow!
It's very cloudy here.
Yeah, as you can see, there's two big chillus
on the left and right.
Hmm, so cute, right?
みんなどうだった？
How was it everyone?
コボのパフォーマンス。
Kobo's performance.
いっぱいスクリーンショット撮れたかな？
Hope you could take lots of screenshots?
コボの新しいステージはどうだった？
How was Kobo's new stage?
可愛いでしょう！
Isn't it cute!
ビッグチルズがありますので、
There are Big Chillus, so
めちゃ可愛いよね！
it's super cute, right!
So, actually...
yeah, we're already at the end of the show, guys.
But...
そろそろお別れの時間になりますよ。
It's almost time to say goodbye.
But don't worry, Kobo still have something to share with you guys.
まだ皆さんに、お知らせがあります！
I still have an announcement for everyone!
ジャン、ジャジャーン！ウィー！
Jan-jan-jaaan! Wheee!
Kobo Kanaeru Special Birthday 2025 Merch Set!
This time, Kobo's birthday merch theme is Jellyfish Princess!
Princess!
I've wanted to wear a jellyfish costume for a long time.
And finally, my wish came true!
So how is it, guys?
Do I look beautiful? Ni-ni-ni-ni.
And the KV is drawn by Scotte-sensei.
スコッティ先生、ありがとう！
Scotte-sensei, thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
And as you wish, guys...
Finally! Ta-da!
Kobokers' happi is here!
Now you guys can be proud Kobokers
and perfect for cheering me during events.
Keren banget.
So cool.
Happi! Happi! Happi!
Come on, buy happi, happi!
And if you look closely, this happi design is like...
...my raincoat, right?
And you can see there's jellies in the front
and me on the back. Right?
And next...
"Jellyfish Princess on the Wall" tapestry.
Wee! It's printed with my brand new birthday illustration.
It's super high quality and perfect for decorating your wall.
You can wake up and see Kobo's smug face every morning.
And also don't forget to praise the Lord every day.
Then look at this!
The "Jellyfish Princess, You Got This" button badge set!
Setto! Two pieces.
Set! Two pieces.
One has my birthday outfit
and the other is an illustration I drew by myself.
Yeah, by myself.
It looks good, right?
Do you like it?
I drew it by myself.
So you can pin them to your bag,
or your hat, or your heart.
Okay. So this one...
...is one of my favorites.
One, two, three, ta-da!
The plushie keychain!
It's me!
But mini Kobo in mini form!
You can bring me anywhere.
On your backpack, your keys,
your motorcycle, the car, or whatever.
Even next to your computer while you watch my streams.
So soft and squishy. An-nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan.
And finally,
we also have the situational voice pack!
So it's called "Your One and Only Jellyfish Princess".
What does it mean?
Buy it! Buy it, okay?
So you know what it means.
Yippie! It's a special voice pack
where I talk to you about Jellyfish Princess
and you know, your one and only, just for you.
Eww... Yeah.
Don't miss out on my birthday merch, guys!
If you buy a set of those, you'll get a special bromide with my signature on it.
The merch is available for a limited time only,
so you can grab yours...
...from the official shop.
Links are in the description.
So yeah, that's all for the announcement.
Thank you for coming and watching Kobo's performance today.
以上、グッズとお知らせでした。
That's all for the merchandise and announcements.
説明欄やチャット欄にリンクを貼ってありますので、
Links are in the description and the chat,
クリックしてね。
so please click them.
おーいよ。But...
Ooi yo. But...
I can hear some of you want an encore? Hmm?
アンコール、アンコール、アンコール欲しい？
Do you want an encore, an encore, an encore?
じゃあ、しょうがないわね。
Well, I guess I have no choice then.
オッケー。
Okay.
Please listen, "Sweet Memories".
Sweet Memories
Lyrics: Matsumoto Takashi / Music: Omura Masaaki
Lyrics: Takashi Matsumoto / Music: Masaaki Omura
Sweet Memories
Lyrics: 松本隆 / Music: 大村雅朗
Lyrics: Takashi Matsumoto / Music: Masaaki Omura
懐かしい
It's a nostalgic
痛みだわ
kind of pain
ずっと前に
That I had forgotten
忘れていた
long ago
でもあなたを
But when I
見たとき
saw you
時間だけ
Only time
あと戻りしたの
seemed to turn back
幸せ？と
Don't ask me
聞かないで
if I'm happy
嘘つくのは
I'm not very good
上手じゃない
at lying
友達なら
I have friends,
いるけれど
but...
あんなには
I can't feel that passion
燃えあがれなくて
anymore
失った
Why is it
夢だけが
that only lost dreams
美しく見えるのは
look so beautiful
なぜかしら
I wonder?
過ぎ去った
Even the kindness
優しさも
that has passed by
今は甘い記憶
Is now a sweet memory
Sweet memories
呼吸（キス）をしたら
If we were to kiss
いけないわ
I shouldn't do it
掟をひとつ
It would only add
増やすだけよ
one more rule
長いあいだ
Even though
あなたに
for so long
逢いたくて泣いていた
I had been crying
くせに
wanting to see you
あの頃は
Back then,
若すぎて
we were too young
いたずらに傷つけあった
and we just hurt each other
ふたり
for no reason
色あせた
Even the faded
悲しみも
sadness
今は遠い記憶
Is now a distant memory
Sweet memories
失った
Why is it
夢だけが
that only lost dreams
美しく見えるのは
look so beautiful
なぜかしら
I wonder?
過ぎ去った
Even the kindness
優しさも
that has passed by
今は甘い記憶
Is now a sweet memory
Sweet memories
フィナーレ
Lyrics: eill / Music: eill, Ryo LEFTY Miyata
Finale
君は本当に
You really
わかってないよ
don't understand
例えばハッピーエンドより
For example, rather than a happy ending...
甘くて豪華なデザートより
Rather than a sweet and luxurious dessert...
君がいいんだよ
I'd rather have you
二つの傘より相合傘
Rather than two umbrellas, sharing one...
ちょっと冷たいけど
It's a bit cold, but...
愛するための代償なら
If it's the price for loving you...
いくらでもどうぞ
Then take as much as you like
ただずっとそばにいたい
I just want to be by your side forever
ねえ、誰も星屑もいない
Hey, in a world where there's no one, not even stardust...
二人ぼっちの世界でずっと
In a world with just the two of us, forever...
最後の花火を上げて
Let's set off the final fireworks...
フィナーレを飾って
And grace the finale
奇跡の降る恋に落ちて
Falling into a love where miracles fall...
誰も離さないで
Don't let anyone go
味気ない世界も悪くないね
This bland world isn't so bad, either
どんなに恋をしたって
No matter how much I fall in love...
出会えないよきっと
I'm sure I'll never encounter it again
終わりもない幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss our endless happiness
いつか今日を
Someday, even if...
忘れても
I forget today...
君がいいんだよ
I'd still want you
天気雨の日 合図して
On a day of sunshower, you gave a sign...
初めて目が合った
...and our eyes met for the first time
ずっと覚えとくよ
I'll remember it forever
ねえ、誰も星屑もいない
Hey, in a world where there's no one, not even stardust...
二人ぼっちの世界でずっと
In a world with just the two of us, forever...
最後の花火を上げて
Let's set off the final fireworks...
フィナーレを誓って
And swear our finale
奇跡の降る恋に落ちて
Falling into a love where miracles fall...
誰も離さないで
Don't let anyone go
そっけない世界も悪くないね
Even a cold world isn't so bad, either
どんなに恋をしたって
No matter how much I fall in love...
忘れられないよきっと
I'm sure I'll never forget it
終わりもない幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss our endless happiness
味気ないね
How bland it is
でもそれがね
But you know, that is...
二人の幸せ
Our happiness
Oh my god, I almost cried.
I almost cried singing this song.
Thank you for today, guys.
Thank you for today, thank you, thank you for watching until the end.
And thank you for Zeta-chi because she covered...
...this finale song first, and then I was inspired, so yeah.
Aku baru lah guna di sini, hehe.
I just used it here, hehe.
Iya iya.
Yes, yes.
今日は来てくれて、最後まで見てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming today and watching until the end!
I hope you guys enjoyed all the performance.
Um, yeah, this whole stream.
みんな大好き！
I love you all!
Thank you for your birthday wishes!
後で読んであげますね。うん。
I'll read them for you later. Yeah.
Bye bye, みんな！
Bye bye, everyone!
No more encore, no more encore.
Bye bye!
Kobo Kanaeru, at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Hehe!
Bye bye!
Ya!
Yay!
Dah!
Bye!
Thank you!
I can't be as bright as now without you!
- Kobo -